Breaker's going to leave mom City Council for Tuesday, July 15th, 2025.
I don't know if to proclamation of clearing July 26th, 2025, is Joe Dawn, Rudy Day.
And maybe no, during the Route 66 area in stressful coming up, that the end of this month,
Joe Dawn, ready to be inducted into local music golfing.
We have some of the folks here tonight to accept this proclamation of work hard on this.
You guys on here.
You guys will say something, tell us all the places we've been trying to do this for like six
years, Joe Dawn, and so it's really good to be able to get to know this and it will
be like a bit of a big thing.
Can we confirm he's out for you, you're going to be here?
I'm not sure, but I'm not sure, but yeah, it's great to have some of the member be ready to
bring some members to the back.
We appreciate the work he does, do you guys carry towards it, not very many or are behind
it on sometimes, so he does do a good job with that, especially on music heritage side.
I'd like to make the gateway to the music, there's some ideas for that.
Not Blux.
If I was thinking of a shower, the shower quit, so I'm going to ask you for a music, I'm from
it's good.
But that's it.
Thank you.
All right.
So I'm leaving the motion to declare July 26, 25, as it's joked on her any day.
Motion.
Second.
So cool.
Hi.
Florence.
He's deaf.
Hi.
Thank you.
That's all right, that's all right.
I'm going to three, I'm going to put on schedule first of all, Francis.
That?
That was supposed to have one.
Ah, I'm glad we know.
Four.
Claims list.
What's your proof?
That's all right.
He said, Barnes, I don't pull.
Hi, Parker.
Hi.
Five minutes from the July 1st, 2025, regular meeting.
Options approved.
Second.
Double.
Barnes, I.
He said, Parker.
Six.
And your financial statements.
And then put it on his report.
So you might want to miss you any from the fiscal year that ended June 30, 2024.
Which is the same thing we heard in the MSUA?
Posted to approve.
Second.
E step.
Hi.
Barnes.
I don't pull.
Hi.
Parker.
Seven.
Approved seniors, center.
Rebranding.
Recommendation by the MIMA seniors.
Seniors.
Incorporated board.
It's got the new logo.
Designed that Sean.
It's worked so hard on.
And so he came back down to the senior center after we was kind of challenged.
Thank you, Hayley.
Because it takes a lot.
I've thanked her many times for being very good at this.
I have a minute.
Can you take another look at this?
And she sent down with us at the Seniors.
And then over.
We're.
We're one of them was.
So.
And I'm telling you.
The senior board is kind of.
They were.
He.
On keeping that.
And so.
We know how they take it.
They're.
So I came back.
We're.
That was.
We brought it back.
And then.
So they.
Totally.
Understand.
He was.
Which they were.
Surprise.
And.
That.
Harder.
Huh?
And.
That.
We.
So.
Yeah.
People.
And so I took into consideration all of the demographics and what we're trying to convey.
And that's why I'm taking these look those all more serious and wanting to go through the different boards.
And because these are two important, you can see the lookers that we use now.
We do four not just two years to the decades.
So it's hard.
Being the love of the waste that's really important to you.
And so I want to thank all of you for coming.
Katie Barnes for this.
We went through the research book.
And these were the initial pulls.
Let's say.
It came out of the research that we did.
So they did everything in that love on it.
And it's research.
She does also everything that I've done.
I'm really impressed.
And he sends it to like a public firm.
And they go on these different things.
And they do that.
They kind of let him know.
They don't want something that looks like a senior citizen.
And so they wanted something vibrant and energetic.
So you can see that.
So this is what we changed it to.
And this is.
Some.
Some lives is instead of the map dot.
Because.
The case concerned was.
That symbol is kind of universal used as an information center.
A map dot will cater.
Those.
I thought we shot to get back.
Change that.
And.
They love this even better.
It looks more like a doorway.
So it's.
It's using the same concept that we all came up with.
That modify it to can take any consideration.
We hope you all like this one.
It was a huge change.
But it was a change in F.
We thought that really.
And they were surprised.
We love this one even more.
I just have to say thank you guys for me.
So open minded and willing to go back to the drawing board.
Because I know that that.
It took a lot of effort.
First time to get there.
And there's.
A lot of concern about.
Oh, man.
We really love this.
Thank you guys for having that open mindset to be able to go back.
And.
We're not something.
It was great teamwork.
Yeah.
We're having difficult.
Perfect connection.
No.
get involved in this process of it and have really exciting me today about the airports.
You know, I'll tell you that the changes were pretty subtle, but big, really.
They didn't really change the look and look on.
I'm glad Ellie spoke up and said something because this is much better.
Even though it's not that much different.
Do you like it much better?
Yeah, just like that. That's why it's important to do.
I'm glad to hear that it wasn't taken personally in that.
I appreciate that you guys are supporting Ellie and her.
Do you don't say?
I don't know what you're going to do.
It works again.
I don't know if I was worried about Ellie and the backlash.
I'm glad it. I'm glad it worked out.
That's good. I love it.
I hate it when you're almost saying yes. That's terrible.
But that tells me that you guys are looking here talking.
You're considering that's it for us.
I'm excited about that.
I didn't even have a long talk about that.
Because it is hard to see a depth when you're going to voice someone.
See all of that. You've been here a while.
So that's why there's five notes.
So because everybody looks at it with different eyes and different thought process.
Sometimes and sometimes they ask questions that I don't even think of.
So it's five of them stuff here.
Honestly, I liked the first one to be honest and didn't consider the standardized shape
as being recognized as something different.
It's so obvious that something we'd advise or ignore.
We can't go on.
It just sticks in younger eyes.
No more clothes.
I'll make a motion.
I'll make a motion. We approve.
Hi.
Thank you.
Thank you, John.
Hey.
Excuse me.
So now, they had some changes to it, most of which were just errors in naming the one that's major
thing that they wanted was the insurance requirements to be that which is required of all
of the tools of the home and I've always wondered that's about our insurance policy.
We require a lot of insurance here, and the school is covered by the governmental torque
concept.
So, I mean, negligence and civil rights violations, somebody's payin' out and they may not
be.
But for just slip-in balls and tors, torped hot stuff, they're covered under the governmental
torque lines act.
So the policy would be chuckest, magnitude, two, and a little bit too thousand, it would
be covered.
The governmental torque lines act as payoff is essentially what it is.
But since they're leasing it from us, there's no way we can get sued through the same
process.
So, if something catastrophic happens, everybody's going to get sued, and then, of course, the
school is going to say, well, it's us and we're going to say, well, it's man, and that would have to
be due to that in court.
I believe that if the school has their leash and the school controls and the schools
responsible for maintenance and upkeep, that the school would be the one responsible for the
liability.
I can't say, no, we won't get sued.
You won't get sued.
If something happens, everybody will get sued, that's just how we're going to work.
We'll wait for it.
We'll make sure it goes well.
We'll be out there.
And we are seriously unsure about what we're going to do, so I'm not worried about it as
what I'm saying.
Okay.
That was really on a change.
That was the only significant change.
I had the school name, drawing in it, so they put the proper name, and there were some
grammatical disagreements between man and their lawyer, but where the comms go on, they don't go.
Semantics.
Motion to approve.
Second.
Circle.
Pardon?
Aye.
Parker.
Go now.
Congratulation.
Senior.
Jackson.
Tanya.
Com range.
Served.
Thank you.
Professor.
Come on.
You can, Danny.
I mean, I though.
I do.
I agree.
Down.
disagree.
Take it.
You want it?
Your story?
Under this?
You for help.
I do have her.
Thank you.
by Tyler Lee Levin, and we have to do this quarterly to keep our ornaments this up today,
and on the government, government, body, and we have to do that.
Much to approve.
Excuse me.
Hi.
I'm Parker.
Ten.
Resolution of CC 2025.
That's your nine support for the point of the mayor of less barker to the district one.
So the board of directors, the local and municipal league, the client's set of point
but to be for the benefit of the city of my mom and other municipalities within the district
and the clearing mission of the local and municipal league to be the public purpose.
We're in the seat that our mayor has been sitting on is up to required by O. Mell and to serve.
I will say, personally, just what I've viewed that networking that we've gotten and the intention
we've gotten.
As you can ask me to say, this is going to decide the more networking with that and that goes for everybody within
the city and you guys on the council and mayor, it's just really important that we do that.
I've seen the value of it just in the three years.
I've been here.
So I just, that's what this ordinance is required for you to do that.
Motion to approve.
All right.
Board.
Time.
E-set.
Parker.
I just think.
11.
Other than the business of any, which is the reason for posting this agenda.
12 staff reports.
I just want to put down one thing in staff.
It's worse that I live in.
Membership is really one of them.
13 mayor.
Council of community and announcements.
I just want to say, what an awesome city we work for.
We've got a bunch of great people working for this city and I don't know.
Anybody ever watches these on on the internet or whatever, but this city is awesome.
We've got a lot of good people that work here and I commend you all.
Thank you for everything everybody does.
Okay.
I want to.
It's really good to know that in my case, I was gone for two weeks, and I know I didn't have to worry, because I knew this community was a good hands-wither without me.
You guys don't need me, and you don't need us up here.
You guys do a great job at what you do.
Towers done a good job of hiring good people to fill spots, and we're just growing together.
That's up here. We get to do the easy part, and you guys get to get your hands dirty, and make us look good up here.
But thank you for what you guys do.
And I know there's a lot of stuff coming up that a lot of people, a lot of departments are going to be working overtime and working out the heat.
And we thank you because our community's going to benefit from that.
And a lot of times they can't see the benefit.
You know, they can't see that everything that's going to be done at the festival is weekend.
It's going to be a lot of blood, sweat, and tears by all of you, so they can have a good time, and they can do it for free.
So thank you for what you guys do.
And I mean, you're going to get this one done, and then you're going to go right on the sidewalk cell, and then it's going to be fair time.
It's going to be rodeo time, and I know you guys are going to be busy, and kids are going to start going to my school.
It's going to be full of time, and the schedule never stops.
But I appreciate everything you guys do, because this city would not move without you guys.
So I know all of your staffs on here, but please pass that along, that we've greatly appreciate all of your efforts, because it takes everyone of you guys to make this community successful.
So, and we've got some really good stuff coming, some really good announcements coming, Tyler and I, it really worked hard on some stuff, and we've been on a couple of them for a year.
And I think we're getting ready to be able to tell all of you about them in their exciting.
Travis knows about some of them, because he's been on that stuff, that there's some really good stuff that's coming out of all the hard work that's put in by everybody.
And it takes a team to get it done, so we appreciate you guys.
14 city manager communication.
I don't have a couple of things.
I've got what the council said.
I mean, it's been a really rough last few weeks.
I don't know if it's been moving or what, but it seems like.
I mean, still be building a way to the library to the senior center, to the streets, to the different things that we've had to go through.
So I appreciate everything that's that has done to keep everything moving forward.
And then Travis is promised me that we're going to start seeing them.
So there's one thing that community really asks for is to start carrying down some of these old, they're like houses.
We're having a community block party, informing us.
We're on the track.
The power's only on the track.
Yes.
Is that how it's been on this track?
No.
We see new yesterdays.
We all want to know when that date is that's one that we have to put a council special appearance
thing out on that one because I think we'll not all want to be there to see that one go down
Who does help hurt up in it and out of it I will I will say
her first round in the she down there she's not a good
who's out in the world
did you run that question sorry